Hello hi everyone is most welcome Radhe
Krishna and guys today I am sharing a
blog on bangles in which I will tell you guys
which bangle
products are available and at what
prices, I will
share all these things with you guys [music] in this blog.
So first of all I get
[music] ready.  So this
outfit of mine [music] I had done it
and after that I go to Judio,
so this is my Judio, so I go to Judio
and [music] I will show you
guys this is the Judio here
[music] and you guys can see
how much greenery there is here.  We have a
lot of greenery [music] in Hyderabad.  So there are many
shops here.  There are many brands.  They are from
Tanish, they are from Max.
Many more shops are available here.  A lot of
[music] from all the brands.  So I had to go to
Judio.  So I went to Judio and
I shot a little bit of my video [music] there.
So I
made this little [music] video in front of what was my studio.
Then after that I am sharing with you guys
what
products [music] are available in the studio.
So here you will get a lot of varieties to
see.  You'll find all varieties of lipstick [music].
Be it glossy,
be it MAC, be it any colour.  All the
things are available to you on Illy pairs.
And its price is ₹149.
You can make any purchase.
Be it matte or glossy [music],
whatever your choices are, you get to see a lot of
varieties [music].  Then
lip glosses are also available here whose
prices are ₹99.  And there's also a combo
that comes in a set of three [MUSIC].
Its price is ₹199.  So here
a lot of varieties of lip gloss are also
available.
And I did a little video of myself here as well.
Then after that I will show you the
primer.  The primers here are also very good [MUSIC].  There are
foundations, there are
nail paints.  So the quality of the nail
paints here [music] is also
very good.  Its
price was ₹99 and
you get to see a lot of color varieties.
After that I am sharing this
kurti which I liked very much.
Its [music] price was only ₹599.
And [Music] All the fabrics in Dudio are of
good quality
and mostly made of cotton [Music].
I really liked this top.
So, yes, there is a lot of variety here for the boys [music].
Like there are
perfumes, there are
outfits [music] and there are a
lot of varieties of shoes.  So boys also do you can
go [music].  You will get to
see varieties at a reasonable
price.  This outfit was quite
casual.  The price of this I [Music]
think was ₹399.  So I was liking it.
And Indian outfits are also seen in it.
[Music] This kurti was priced at 300.
So
you get all the sections of music in the studio, be it Indian or Western.
Also, there were a lot of varieties of kids wear kids.  At very reasonable
prices.  The [music] varieties of all the products on the pairs are
quite good.
The prices are also correct.  It is not that they are
very costly.  Then this was one
set that I really liked.  So
I tried two outfits here.
[MUSIC]
So, here's the first one I really liked.
Its fabric is cotton fabric.  The
work done in this is quite decent.
So I liked this outfit.
Second [music] I tried this one.
It was set to one.  So [music] the
print of it looked pretty good.
So I tried these two [music].
I tried some more and
purchased some of them.  [MUSIC]
Then I get out of the pairs.
Maxis brand is here.
Next to it was [MUSIC] Burger King where I had to
go.  So I quickly go to Burger
King and we have [music]
French fry burgers and cold drinks.
So this is the Burger King here that I
went to [MUSIC].  And
now I am sharing with you all what things I have purchased.
I will show you one by one all the Joe's products I have purchased,
which products I have
purchased from Joe.  I am sharing its reviews
with you all in this video and
since the festival seasons are coming now, I
hope this video will be useful for you all
because many people do not know
where which products are
available at what prices.  So if you buy them online,
you can get the pairs at the best price.  There are
many varieties in it.  Be it dresses or
beauty products.   There are a
lot of varieties in this.   The
end price is also quite reasonable.   It is
absolutely reasonable.  You get a lot of varieties.
You have a lot of options
[music].  So,
I am sharing with you all
in this video the special purchase that I have made.  Hope you guys
like what I purchased
from JDO.  So I will show one by one
which products I have purchased.  And
I am sharing its review with you all
in this [music] blog.  And
if anyone has any queries, skin
related or related to anything else,
if you have any queries, any
questions, then you
can definitely comment to me.  just ask me.
I reply to everyone [MUSIC].  So,
if you guys have any queries then please
comment me.  I will
definitely give you guys suggestions from my [music] side.
So first of all I would
like to tell you that there are many varieties of liners.
Meaning if you
want any color eyeliner, blue color, brown color,
all colors are available.  What I have purchased,
I have purchased one in black
colour and one in brown colour.
Black and brown.  Black color is the one
which is always used and it is completely water
proof.  These liners are very good.
What I've just applied
[music] is also the online
application for this.  So I'm sharing a demo of this
with you guys
[music] because I don't share every product,
I like it in videos.
So let me show you, I am
applying it on my hands.   You
can check out this liner [music].   It is
water proof.  It is quite long lasting.
So I think its price is
also ₹100.  All the online
liners available on this platform are priced at ₹100
only.  So you can take any color.
You will get Eli for ₹100.  Then
after that [music] I also got this new one from Oliner
which is coming on.  This is also of black colour.
This has just been newly launched.  Then there was a
good variety of clutches there.
So I have purchased these ones.
Then after that I have bought a bracelet
because I do
n't wear bangles much.  So this type of bracelets that you
can see [music], these types of
bracelets look good
with all the dresses, be it western dress or Indian dress.
So here
you guys can see [music].  I have purchased this.
I bought lipstick
[MUSIC] this one.
And I have purchased a highlighter.
I am demonstrating this by applying it
on my hands.  [Music]
Look, here's a lighter.
[Music]
So I purchased this one from JDO.   Then
I told you that one good thing
in JDO is that you can buy any lip balm there.
Its price is only ₹50.
So I have purchased this one.
Its price is ₹50 [Music].
So the variety of products available at very reasonable prices is
also good.  The
fabrics that remain are also
mostly cotton fabrics.  So I
think you have very good options.
If you want to go and purchase it,
you can definitely go.  You
can see it and now it is the festival season so
many offers are also going on on Judio.  So
you guys can definitely watch it.
And look at this.  [MUSIC] This is lip balm.   It is
only ₹50.   The finish
is very long lasting and leaves your lips feeling
glossy [MUSIC].  So
this is Juddo's lip balm.  So I
purchased all these things from Dudio.
I have shared the demo of the end dress with you all
in the video itself.  And one dress
I didn't share is this one.
I bought a dress.  Because I like black
and white colors very much [music].
So I had purchased a shirt, this one in
black colour.  [Music] I'll
share a demo of this as well in shots in upcoming videos.
So this was my Jo's shopping and
my Jo's blog, if you liked it then
please like, share and
subscribe to the channel.  And
thank you so much everyone.  To all the people who
support me, [music] to all the people who
watch my videos,
thank you from the bottom of my heart.  And if you guys watch the videos
then please do hype it
with likes.  And thank you so much to
everyone.  Radhe Krishna.  Bye-by take care.